

Jordan Heersink

Full Stack Web Developer

Profile

Full-stack web developer seeking to apply eight years of previous IT expertise to the web. Proficient at taking end users' needs and transforming them into workable solutions to fit their style. Able to listen to non-technical users' requests and translate them to a team of highly technical developers to work on solutions. Have a love for technology, learning, and problem-solving. Looking to bring a commitment to excellence and a hard work ethic to a company and become a valuable asset.

Employment History

ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT OF TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Colorado Christian University | Lakewood, CO

January 2015 - Present

- Lead the University's IT support division
- Develop strategies for quickly resolving end user's technical issues
- Manage the department's hiring, firing, and budgeting responsibilities
- Purchase and implement new technology for all the university's campuses
- Forecast solutions for other department's technological business needs

AFFILIATE PROFESSOR

Colorado Christian University | Lakewood, CO

August 2020 - May 2022

- Instructing a Computer Information Systems course
- Consistently achieving high student reviews

EVENT COORDINATOR

Colorado Christian University | Lakewood, CO

May 2008 - December 2014

- Led the team responsible for numerous campus projects and events
- Managed and ran the AV productions of large events
- Captured, organized, and analyzed critical department-related data

Education

edX Full Stack Development Bootcamp Certificate

Denver University | Denver, CO

December 2023 - June 2024

Masters of Business Administration with an emphasis in Leadership

Colorado Christian University | Lakewood, CO

January 2015 - May 2017

3.98 GPA out of 4.0

Bachelors of Science in Information Systems Management

Colorado Christian University | Lakewood, CO

January 2011 - October 2014

- Dean's List recipient for each semester
- 4.0 GPA out of 4.0 in degree program courses

References

Dan Cohrs Colorado Christian University 303-324-9673

Paul Ji Snowflake 408-691-0009

Details

- Castle Rock, Colorado
- 303.842.6939
- heersink.jordan@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/jordanheersink/

Skills

Git

00000

HTML & CSS 00000

Bootstrap

JavaScript

jQuery

00000

Web Services APIs

•••00

Node.js

••••

Express.js

•••00

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

••••

React

Leadership

Problem Solving

00000

Communication

Project Management

••••

Time Management

